nehruplacemarket.com 2018-11-12

# Privacy Policy - NehruPlace Market - Latest Computer Hardware Price List - Nehru Place IT Hub

|   
Privacy Policy

 **We respect your privacy. This statement discloses the information gathering process and the privacy and dissemination practices for NehruPlaceMarket.com, On NehruPlaceMarket.com we generally do not collect the personal information (like your name, email id, contact number, address details etc.) of an ordinary site visitor. The ordinary visitor means if you are not a registered dealer / user of the website www.NehruPlaceMarket.com, We are able to get the information about your internet browser details, ISP   and IP address details in case you are an ordinary user. But if you are a registered user, while your registeration we collect your personal information (like your name, email id, contact number, address details etc.) which you fill in the registration form on the website for your dealer profile purpose. But it is for sure we do not share or sell any information about the registered users/ dealers or ordinary visitors of this website NehruPlaceMarket.com to any body. However, we may send you our own promotional offers emails, news letters and other emails realted to nehruplacemarket.com or other sites.

Also, we do analyise the visitors data on our website to further improve the website content and apperance. For this Nehruplacemarket.com uses few third party services like stat-counter, google analytics etc. to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on this site. This information helps us understand visitors interests and helps us improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed. StatCounter does not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes. Also you can see the privacy policies of these service providers by visitng their respective websites like for privacy ploicy of Statcounter visit statcounter.com, for google analytics visit google.com and so on. We have our [Cookie Policy](http://www.nehruplacemarket.com/cookie-policy.html) which tells about how we use cookies on our website. Please do read our [Cookie Policy by clicking here](http://www.nehruplacemarket.com/cookie-policy.html) as a part of document. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site and may use this non-personally identifiable information (i.e. information not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This information may include the number of impressions, your web browser information, browser type, your IP Address details, click stream information, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. However, you can disable cookies easily from your web browser settings/ options. If you would like more information about this behavioral advertising practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies you can visit this website www.networkadvertising.org 

**  

|
